pdfescape.com 2019-11-18

# PDFescape Privacy Policy

Effective July 30 2019

## Red Software Websites

The following websites ("Red Software Websites") are operated by Red Software ("we" or "us") and governed by this privacy policy: 

  * [https://www.pdfescape.com](https://www.pdfescape.com/) ("PDFescape Website") 

## General Information

We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices. 

  * This policy covers what information we collect and how it is treated. 
  * This policy only applies to Red Software Websites and does not extend to the practices of other websites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

## Contact Information

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy. 

You may contact us using the information provided on our website. 

## Dispute Resolution

We are committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently. 

Concerns will be responded to promptly by our customer service representatives. 

## Information Collection

When visiting Red Software Websites, certain information about you and your devices can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information Red Software collects, and how it is used. 

### Information Collected

What information do we collect? 

We collect and use the following information to provide, improve, protect, and promote Red Software Websites and our related services (e.g. PDFescape Desktop): 

  * _Account Information_ – We may collect, and associate with an account, information including your name, email address, phone number, payment info, and billing address. 
  * _Cookies_ – We use cookies and similar technologies to do things like log you into your account on a Red Software Website, remember your settings, or help us test out promotions and improvements. 
  * _Customer Data_ – We may store, process, and transmit your data (including metadata, files, settings, etc.). When using the PDFescape Website, you can [manage your files in your account](https://www.pdfescape.com/account/pdfs/); if your file is not associated with a PDFescape account, it is typically removed from our servers after forty-eight (48) hours of inactivity. 
  * _Usage_ – We may collect information from and about the devices you use to access Red Software Websites. This information includes IP addresses, the type of browser you are using, the web pages visited on Red Software Websites, the web page which referred you to a Red Software Website, and identifiers associated with your devices (which may include their location depending upon your device settings). 

### Information Recipients

Who has access to the information collected? 

We may share information as discussed below, but we won't sell it to advertisers or other third-parties. 

  * _Others Working for Red Software_ – We use certain trusted third parties to help us provide, improve, protect, and promote Red Software Websites and our related services. These third parties will access your information only to perform tasks on our behalf. 
  * _Other Applications_ – We offer tools on Red Software Websites allowing Account Information and Customer Data to be shared with third party applications (e.g. Google Drive). If using such an application, please remember that their use of your information will be governed by their policies and terms. 
  * _Other Visitors_ – We offer tools on Red Software Websites allowing Customer Data to be published or shared. Data shared using these tools, obviously, will be available to other visitors with valid credentials (e.g. the URL). 
  * _Legal Authorities_ – We may disclose your information to third parties if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with the law; (b) protect any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of a Red Software Website or our users; or (d) protect our property rights. 

### Information Retention

How long is this information retained? 

  * Account Information and Customer Data may be retained by us for as long as we need it to provide you services, or as required by law. 
  * Cookies are stored by your browser and can be cleared using your browser's preferences at any time. 
  * Usage is typically archived for a minimum of 1 year to help improve and secure Red Software Websites. 

### Cookie Policy

Typically, cookies are stored by your browser when visiting Red Software Websites. Most browsers can be configured to disable cookies, but you may not be able to access all features and portions of Red Software Websites. Cookies are used for various reasons on Red Software Websites: 

  * _Security_ – These cookies allow us to keep you signed in, securely identify your browser session, and help prevent attacks. 
  * _Preferences_ – These cookies help us to remember your preferences (e.g. preferred language) for use on Red Software Websites. 
  * _Analytics_ – These cookies allow us to understand how you engage with Red Software Websites. You can [install this tool from Google to opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) of these cookies. 
  * _Advertising_ – These cookies help us to serve you engaging and relevant advertising. You can [opt-out of these cookies](http://optout.aboutads.info/). 

### Google Adwords, AdSense, Analytics, and reCAPTCHA

Google AdWords is a program run by Google that delivers advertisements promoting Red Software Websites and other websites across the Internet. Google AdSense is a program run by Google that delivers advertisements displayed on Red Software Websites. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google that is in use on Red Software Websites. Google reCAPTCHA is a website protection service provided by Google that is in use on Red Software Websites. Google may utilize the data collected to track and examine the use of Red Software Websites, to prepare reports on its activities, and to share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Google may collect cookie and usage data. Google may share this information with other parties. Google's privacy policy can be found at <https://policies.google.com/privacy>. 

Red Software Websites may implement some Google Analytics Advertising Features, including Remarketing with Google Analytics. Remarketing (using things like cookies) helps third party vendors like Google to advertise and promote our products and services based on your past visits to Red Software Websites. You can opt out of the Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google's Ad Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/). 

## Do Not Track

Red Software Websites do not currently respond to a Do Not Track ("DNT") or similar signal. 

## Policy Changes

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy from time to time. 

Changes to our privacy policy will be accessible at <https://www.pdfescape.com/privacy/>

## Terms of Use

All information collected by a Red Software Website is subject to our Terms of Use. If there is a conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, the Terms of Use shall control. 

This website uses cookies to keep you signed in, deliver advertisements, improve user experience, and more. By using this website, you are agreeing to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy (updated July 30 2019).  
Learn More

Got it!
